freehookupsearch.com 2017-12-12

# Free Hookup Search Privacy Policy

* **What kind of information do we collect?** In general, we may collect information that can identify you such as your name and email address and other information that does not identify you. We may collect this information through our Website or a mobile application. When you provide personal information through our Website or mobile application, the information may be sent to servers located in the United States and other countries throughout the world. If you do not register and just visit the Website, we do not collect any personal information about you, but we will place session ID cookies on your computer. For more information about cookies generally, look at the answer to “ _How do we use cookies and other technical information?_ ” below. 

**_Information you provide._** We may collect and store any personal information you enter in our Website or on a mobile application, or provide to us in some other manner. This includes personal information such as your name, address, email address, and telephone number, and if you transact business with us, financial information such as your payment method (valid credit card number, type, expiration date, or other financial information). You may also provide us information about your interests and activities, your gender and age, and other demographic information such as your hometown and your screen name. 

**_Information from other sources._** **** Free Hookup Search is a part of a dating network operated by WishLand Services Ltd. We may obtain both personal and nonpersonal information about you from other websites operated by our company, business partners, contractors, and other third parties. We may also receive information about our users from third-party social networking platforms. When you access or use our Website or mobile application through a third party, you allow us to access or collect information made available by the third party according to the third party’s privacy policy. This information may be available from your profile or account with that third party or from cookies placed on your device by that third party.  

**_Information collected from mobile devices._** We offer you the opportunity to stay in touch with the friends and contacts you have made wherever you are. You can do this by using your mobile phone or by downloading our mobile application that allows you to share your location with other users. If you access our Website through a mobile device (for example, smartphone, tablet, etc.), we also may collect your unique device identifier and mobile device IP address, as well as information about your mobile device’s operating system, mobile carrier, mobile Internet browser, WiFi access points, your precise geographic location (including longitude and latitude), and other information described in this privacy policy. If you do not want your location known, you can turn off location services on your mobile device by going to “(1) settings, (2) location services, (3) off” for iOS devices and “(1) profile, (2) privacy, (3) on” for Android devices. 

**_Information about others_**. We may collect and store personal information about other people that you provide to us, such as their name, address, and email address. If you use our Website to send others (friends, relatives, colleagues, etc.) a product as a gift, we may store your personal information, and the personal information of each recipient in order to process those requests or facilitate future activities.

**_Technical and usage information._** **** We also collect certain nonpersonal information when you use our Website. For example, we collect information on the type of browser you are using, the type of operating system you are using, the domain name of your Internet service provider or mobile carrier, IP address, and certain usage information including the locations of the webpages that you viewed right before arriving at, while navigating, and immediately after leaving the Website. 

**_DMCA infringement notices, notices of violations of Website terms, and other communications directed to us_**. By submitting a copyright infringement notice or other communication (including communications about content stored on or transmitted through the Website), you consent to have these communications forwarded to the person or entity who stored, transmitted, or linked to the content addressed by your communication, in order to facilitate a prompt resolution. For notices of violations of Website terms or other communications (but not DMCA infringement notices), on request we will edit out your name and contact information. But we may forward DMCA infringement notices (including any personal information contained in the notices) as submitted to us without any deletions.

 ** _Providing requested information._** **** In some cases, only persons who provide us with the requested personal information will be able to order products and services, or otherwise participate in the Website’s offerings.   

* **Who sees your personal information?** We do not share your personal information with others except as indicated here or when we inform you and give you an opportunity to opt-out of having your personal information shared. We may share your personal information as follows:  
**_  
Legal and law enforcement purposes._** We may disclose your personal information in response to legal process, including court orders and subpoenas, or in response to a law enforcement agency's request. We also may disclose your information to third parties for fraud detection and prevention activities. Finally, we may disclose your personal information if necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of another person, violations of any of our terms or other policies, to protect our rights and the rights of others, or as otherwise required by law. ****  
**_  
Change of control._** We may transfer any information about you as part of substantial corporate transactions, such as the sale of our business, a divesture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy.  
**_  
Vendors and service providers._** We may share your information, including personal information, with third parties that perform certain services on our behalf. These services may include fulfilling orders, providing customer service and marketing assistance, performing business and sale analysis, ad tracking and analytics, member screenings (although see our terms about not conducting criminal background checks), supporting our website functionality, and other features offered through our Website. We may also share your name, contact information, and credit card information with our service providers who process credit card payments. These service providers may have access to personal information needed to perform their functions but are not permitted to share or use this information for any other purposes.  
**_  
Business partners._** When you register or make purchases on our Website or click-through our advertisements offered on third-party websites or applications, we may share your personal information with the businesses with which we collaborate to offer you the applicable products, services, or any advertisements. When you elect to engage in a particular merchant’s offer or program, you authorize us to provide your email address and other information to that merchant.  
**_  
Advertisement servers._** At our Website, third parties may present or serve advertisements, provide us with data collection, reporting, ad response measurement, and website analytics, as well as assist with delivery of relevant marketing messages and advertisements. These third parties may view, edit, or set their own cookies. The use of these technologies by these third parties is subject to their own privacy policies and governed by this privacy policy. They may also obtain information about other applications that you have downloaded to your mobile device, the mobile websites you visit, and other information about you or your device in order to help analyze and serve anonymous targeted advertising on the Website and elsewhere.   
**_  
Aggregated or nonpersonal information_**. We may share your nonpersonal information we collect under any of the above circumstances. We may also share it with other companies and third parties to develop and deliver targeted advertising on our Website and on websites or applications of third parties, and to analyze and report on advertising you see. We may combine nonpersonal information we collect with additional nonpersonal information collected from other sources. 
* **How do we use your information?**

**_Providing our products and services._** We use the information we collect about you: (1) to fulfill your requests for our products, programs, and services; (2) to respond to your inquiries about our offerings; (3) to provide, personalize, and improve our offerings; and (4) to offer you other products, programs, or services from us and our affiliates, business partners, and selected third parties that we believe may be of interest to you. We may also use information that we collect about you to (1) perform research and analysis about your use of, or interest in, our products, services, or content, or products, services, or content offered by others; or (2) develop and display content and advertising tailored to your interests on our Website and other websites, including providing our advertisements to you when you visit other websites. 

We use the information we collect for our online forums and communities to provide an interactive experience. We use this information to facilitate participation in these online forums and communities and, on one or more occasions, to offer you products, programs, or services.

If you choose to submit content, we may publish your screen name and other information you have provided to us on our Website, the Internet, or elsewhere.   
**_  
Communications._** We use information about you to communicate with you, including: (1) to notify you when we make changes to our terms; (2) to otherwise enforce or exercise any rights in our terms; (3) to fulfill a request by you for an online newsletter; (4) to confirm purchasers you have made through our Website; or (4) to contact you about your account with us (including managing your account and providing you with customer support). If offered, you may also choose to receive push notifications from us on your mobile device. **Please note that any communications from other users are through our internal systems, which we use to match the message to you and generate an email notice without disclosing any information aside from your chosen screen name and the information contained in your profile.**

We use the information that you provide about others to allow us to send them invitations, gifts, cards, or other content on your behalf or through our Website. Occasionally, we also may use this information to offer products, programs, or services to them.  
**_  
Mobile device data usage._** When you access our Website on a mobile device, we may use the information collected for any purpose stated in this privacy policy.  
**_  
Use of nonpersonal information._** We use aggregate information about our users and nonpersonal information that we collect to improve the design, functionality, and content of our Website and to allow us to personalize your experience with our Website and offerings. We use this information: (1) to provide, maintain, personalize, protect, improve, and develop our products, programs, and services and to operate our business; (2) to analyze usage and performance of our Website (including to perform ad tracking and website or mobile application analytics); and (3) for us and our affiliates, business partners, and selected third parties to offer you products, programs, or services. 

* **How do we use cookies and other technical information?**

**_Cookies and Web beacons._** Third-party service providers, our business partners, our affiliates, and we may send “cookies” to your computer (or mobile device) or use similar technologies to enhance your online experience at our Website. “Cookies” are a string of information that a website stores on a user’s computer (or mobile device), and that the user’s browser provides to the website each time the user submits a query to the website. Cookies can identify you as a unique customer and store your personal preferences as well as technical information. Cookies manage and measure the performance of advertisements displayed on or delivered by or through us or other networks or websites. Cookies can either be persistent (that is, they remain on your computer until you delete them) or temporary (that is, they last only until you close your browser). Cookies on our Website do not link to or store your personal information.

For example, when you sign in to our Website, we will record your user or member ID and the name associated with your user or member ID in the cookie file on your computer. We also may record your password in this cookie file, if you told us that you would like your password saved for automatic sign-in. For security purposes, we encrypt account-related data that we store in these cookies. For websites and services that do not use a user or member ID, the cookie will contain a unique identifier. We may use persistent tracking cookies on your mobile device, mainly for security protection purposes, such as to prevent phishers, scammers, unauthorized log in attempts, and to help you access your hacked account. We may allow our service providers to serve cookies from our Website or application to allow them to assist us in various activities, such as doing analysis and research on the effectiveness of our Website, content, and advertising. 

Our Website may use locally stored objects (sometimes referred to as “Flash cookies”) to provide certain content, such as video on demand, video clips, or animation. The Adobe Flash Player and similar applications use this technology to remember settings, preferences, and usage similar to browser cookies. Flash cookies are not managed through your browser, but you can access your Flash management tools from [Adobe’s website](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html).

We may also use “Web beacons” that monitor your use of our Website. “Web beacons” (also known as clear gifs, pixel tags, or Web bugs) are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of users or to access cookies. Unlike cookies, which are stored on the user’s device, Web beacons are embedded invisibly on the webpages (or in email) and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We use Web beacons to collect the following information: (1) the IP (Internet Protocol) address of the computer that downloaded the webpage on which the Web beacon appears; (2) the URL (Uniform Resource Locator) of the webpage on which the Web beacon appears; (3) the time the webpage containing the Web beacon was viewed; (4) the types of browser that fetched the Web beacon; and (5) the identification number of any cookie on the computer previously placed by that server. 

When corresponding with you through HTML capable email, Web beacons let us know whether you received and opened our email.

On their own, cookies or Web beacons do not contain or reveal any personal information. But if you choose to furnish personal information, this information can be linked to the data stored in the cookies/Web beacons.

 ** _Managing cookies and Web beacons._** By accepting this privacy policy, you agree to our use of cookies and Web beacons as described in this privacy policy. You may adjust your browser to reject cookies from us or from any other website. Additionally, by setting your browser to display HTML emails as text only, you may be able to prevent the use of some Web beacons. Please consult the “Help” section of your browser for more information. Please understand that you can only access certain areas of our Website in conjunction with cookies or similar devices and you should be aware that disabling cookies or similar devices might prevent you from accessing some of our content or Website features. **You assume all responsibility for any resulting loss of functionality because of disabling cookies or similar devices.**

* **Do you have any choices about collection and use of your information?** You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but that may result in you being unable to use certain features of our Website because that information may be required in order for you to register as a member; purchase products or services; participate in a live interaction or promotion; ask a question; or initiate other transactions. 

When you register on our Website, you consent to receive email messages from us. You may modify this consent later by visiting the “[Account Settings](http://www.freehookupsearch.com/account/)” page associated with your account. You can always choose to no longer receive commercial or promotional emails from us by visiting the “[Account Settings](http://www.freehookupsearch.com/account/)” page associated with your account. You also will have the opportunity, in any commercial email that we send to you, to opt-out of receiving any similar messages in the future. Online opt-out requests are instant; it may take up to postal procedure/time frame and 15 days for any offline by mail opt-out requests. However, we may send you transactional and relationship emails, such as service announcements and administrative notices, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receive them. 

Our mobile applications may also deliver notices to your phone or mobile device. You can disable these notices in your device’s settings, in your account under “[Account Settings](http://www.freehookupsearch.com/account/),” or by deleting the relevant mobile application. 

You can also control information collected by cookies. Please see our discussion of cookies above for information about declining or deleting cookies. 

* **What is “Do Not Track” and does the Website follow it?** Do Not Track (“DNT”) is a privacy preference that you can set in your Web browser. DNT is a way for you to inform websites and services that you do not want certain information about your webpage visits collected over time and across websites or online services. We are committed to providing you with meaningful choices about the information we collect and that is why we provide you the ability to opt-out. However, we do not recognize or respond to any DNT signals as the Internet industry works toward defining exactly what DNT means, what it means to comply with DNT, and a common approach to responding to DNT.
* **How secure is your personal information?** We take reasonable administrative, physical, and electronic measures designed to safeguard and protect your information from unauthorized access or disclosure. This includes using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts the personal information you input, and storing your information in encrypted form behind a firewall designed to block access from outside our network. 

Although we use commercially reasonable efforts to safeguard the privacy of your information, transmissions on the Internet cannot be made absolutely secure. Moreover, we cannot assure you that your personal information that we collect will not be used or disclosed inconsistently with this privacy policy. We assume no responsibility or liability for disclosure of any of your information due to errors in transmission, unauthorized third-party access, or other causes beyond our reasonable control.

* **What about other websites linked to our Website?** There are places on the Website where you can click on a link to access other websites. For example, if you click on an advertisement on our Website, you may be taken to a third-party website. These third-party websites may independently solicit and collect information, including personal information, from you and, in some instances, provide us with information about your activities on those websites. Third parties are under no obligation to comply with this privacy policy concerning personal information that you provide directly to those third parties or that those third parties collect for themselves. We neither own nor control third-party websites accessible through our Website. Thus, this privacy policy does not apply to information provided to or gathered by third parties that operate them. We assume no responsibility for the content or the privacy policies of any other websites that may provide links to our Website or to whom we may provide links, or for the privacy policies of any of their advertisers. Before visiting a third-party website, whether by means of a link on this Website or otherwise, and before providing any personal information to any third party, you should inform yourself of the privacy policies any practices (if any) of the third party responsible for that website, and should take those steps necessary to, in your discretion, protect your privacy. 
* **What about information you provide about yourself while using our Website?** We have designed the Website to make it easy for you to find, connect, and interact with other members of the Website by posting information about yourself. You can also use our electronic messaging system, which allows you to communicate with other users provided you are both subscribers. We recommend and encourage you (and all our members) to think carefully about the information they disclose about themselves. We also do not recommend that you put email addresses, URLs, instant messaging details, phone numbers, full names or addresses, credit card details, national identity numbers, drivers’ license details, and other sensitive information in your profile, which is open to abuse and misuse. 

Please be careful about posting sensitive details about yourself on your profile such as your religious denomination and health details. While you may voluntarily provide this information to us when you create your profile, including your sexual preferences and ethnic background, there is no requirement to do so. Please remember that photographs or any video clips that you post on the Website may reveal these kinds of sensitive personal data. Where you do upload and choose to tell us sensitive information about yourself, you are explicitly consenting to our processing your information and making this public to other users. 

When you post information about yourself or use the messaging service, the amount of personal information you share is at your own risk. In addition, these postings may appear on other websites or in searches on the subject matter of your posting. Whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information on publicly-viewable webpages, you make that information publicly available and others can collect and use that information. For example, if you post your email address, you may receive unsolicited email messages. If you post anything that is inconsistent with our terms, we reserve the right to terminate your account. 

Bottom line: **We cannot control who reads your posting or what other users may do with the information you voluntarily post, so we encourage you to exercise discretion and caution for your personal information.**

* **What information does the Website collect about children?** You may only use the Website if you are aged 18 or over or the age of majority in the country in which reside if that happens to be greater than 18. That means we do not knowingly collect any information about children, minors, or anyone under the age of majority. Nor do we knowingly market to children, minors, or anyone under the age of 18. If you are less than 18-years old, we request that you do not submit information to us. If we become aware that a child, minor, or anyone under the age of 18 has registered with us and provided us with personal information, we will take steps to terminate that person’s registration and delete that person’s profile information from the Website. If we do delete a profile because you violated our no children rules, we may retain your email and IP address to ensure that you do not try to get around our rules by creating a new profile. 

Our Website is also [RTA®](http://www.rtalabel.org/) labeled and will not be visible if your computer is child protected. If minors have access to your computer, please restrain their access to sexually explicit material by using any of the following products provided for informational purposes only and not endorsed by us: [CYBERsitter™](http://www.cybersitter.com/) | [Net Nanny®](http://www.netnanny.com/) | [CyberPatrol](http://www.cyberpatrol.com/) | [ASACP](http://www.asacp.org/).

* **Do special rules apply to California residents?** Yes. If you are a California resident, you have the right to receive: (1) information identifying any third party company to whom we may have disclosed, within the past calendar year, personal information concerning you and your family for our direct marketing purposes; and (2) a description of the categories of personal information disclosed. You must make a request in writing to us to obtain this information. We will not process your request unless it includes your name and email address, the URL for the website you visited, and a return address. We will only honor one request per calendar year. Please contact our [customer support staff](http://www.freehookupsearch.com/help/) to make your request.
* **How do you update or correct your information?** If you have an online account with us, you have the ability to review and update your personal information online by logging into [your account and clicking on your account settings](http://www.freehookupsearch.com/account/). If you have an online account with us, you also may close your account at any time by [contacting our support](http://www.freehookupsearch.com/help/) for this request. If you close your account, we may retain certain information associated with your account for analytical purposes and recordkeeping integrity, as well as to prevent fraud, collect any fees owed, enforce our terms, take actions we deem necessary to protect the integrity of our website or our users, or take other actions otherwise permitted by law. In addition, if certain information has already been provided to third parties as described in this privacy policy, retention of that information will be subject to those third parties’ policies. 
* **Do third parties have any rights under this privacy policy?** No. This privacy policy does not create rights enforceable by third parties or require disclosure of any personal information relating to users of the Website.
* **Can we change this privacy policy?** We will amend this privacy policy on one or more occasions, as we believe necessary or convenient to operate our Website. When we post changes to this privacy policy, we will revise the “last updated” date at the top of this privacy policy. We will use all commercially reasonable efforts to provide you with advance notice of any change by posting notice of the amended privacy policy on this webpage at least 30 days before its effective date. We will keep prior versions of this privacy policy in an archive for your review. Unless we obtain your express consent, any revised privacy policy will apply only to information collected after its effective date, and not to information collected under any earlier privacy policies. We encourage you to frequently check this webpage for any changes to this privacy policy. If you do not agree to our amended privacy policy, you must cancel your membership before or after the amended privacy policy becomes effective as provided in the terms or otherwise stop using this Website. If we do not hear from you, we will assume, and you agree, that your continued access to our Website after the amended privacy policy’s effective date forms your acceptance of our amended privacy policy, and thus the amended privacy policy will govern your access to or use of the Website after the effective date.
* **What law and language govern this privacy policy?** Republic of Cyprus law governs this privacy policy and any dispute or claim arising out of or in connection with it or its subject matter (including noncontractual disputes or claims). If a discrepancy exists between this English language version of the privacy policy and any translated copies of the privacy policy, the English version will prevail. 
* **What if you have more questions or want to contact us?** If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policy, our practices, or your dealings with us, please use the [customer support](http://www.freehookupsearch.com/help/) form on our Website and our team will deal with your inquiry quickly, professionally, and efficiently because we take the privacy of our members seriously and are ready to address all the concerns they may have.
